But do you imagine, reverend sir, that marriages can be made like omelets? A fortnight in Venice, that is nothing; you ought to live there at least six months. Now, for instance, I think your niece sweetly pretty, and I should consider myself fortunate if the wife whom God intends for me were like her, but, even if she offered me now a dowry of fifty thousand crowns on condition that our wedding takes place immediately, I would refuse her. A prudent young man wants to know the character of a girl before he marries her, for it is neither money nor beauty which can ensure happiness in married life.

唐僧：噢，你想要啊？你想要说清楚不就行了吗？你想要的话我会给你的，你想要我当然不会不给你啦！不可能你说要我不给你，你说不要我却偏要给你，大家讲道理嘛！现在我数三下，你要说清楚你要不要......