A 《大话西游》经典台词：中英日语混编（Chinese+English+Japanese)
   曾经有一份真诚的love放在我面前，私はそれを大切にしなかった，等我失去的时候我才regret，人世间最痛苦的事莫过于此。
   神が私に再びそれを行う機会を与えることができれば，我会对那个girl说三个字：我爱你。
   如果非要在这份爱上加上一个期限，我希望是……
   10000+年

B  Elizabeth washes her hands every day. She likes to wash her hands. She washes her hands with soap and water. She washes her hands for 30 seconds. After 30 seconds, she stops washing her hands. She turns off the water. She dries her hands on a clean towel. 